Mss.Ms.Coll.104
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Correspondence-Hare Family, 1724-1965
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1891 February 3; No. 854
    Arrived after visit home. Send check. Anxious to get photo of Ava Willing. Hope you can come to New York so we can see Sarah Bernhart. Hopes Grandpapa consents to our going abroad.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 February 8; No. 855
    Photos. Send check. Wants to see Sarah Bernhart. Mrs. Whitney at Carmencita Ball - worse than French Ball. Saw Cram in "The Senator".
  - Elsie to Miss Esther Hare, 1891 February 15; No. 856
    Sights - Mardigras and Gobelin Tapestry Works. Got apartment and went to Julian's studio.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 February 16; No. 857
    Received check - all went for bills and no money left. Wants to come home over Washington's birthday, but no money, so could you come to New York and we could see Sarah Bernhart. Disgusted with college. Lost $10. gambling.
  - Horace B. Hare to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 February 16; No. 858
    Journey there and description of place. Letters to "Duck" and "Addie".
  - Cass to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 February 17; No. 859
    Read enclosed pamphlet entitled "Wayside Ministries". St. Agnes Guild and giving ourselves to God during Lent. Painters and paintings.
  - Mother to "Dearest Horace", 1891 February 21; No. 860
    Hope you are enjoying yourself with Grandpapa on fishing and hunting trip. Ava Willing's wedding.
  - Horace B. Hare to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 February 21; No. 861
    Journey from Kissimmee to St. James City. Brochure of San Carlos Hotel, St. James, Florida.
  - Elsie Beale to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 February 22; No. 862
    Picnic. Bongereau at studio looking at my drawings.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 February 25; No. 863
    Gave up idea of coming home over weekend. Received wedding cake. Are we going abroad?
  - Mary R. Coles to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 March 2; No. 864
    Travels - 2 months of study in Paris, south of Italy, Cairo, Pyramids, presented to Khediva, tombs at Sakkara, to Greece and plans to go to Constantinople, Vienna and Paris. About friends.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 March 2; No. 865
    About going abroad. Sarah Bernhart to be in Philadelphia. Kept promise - not playing cards. Send check and would like White Mountain cake.
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 March 5; No. 866
    About expense account for year sent to Grandpapa and your going abroad.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 March 13; No. 867
    Needs more money. Saw Sarah Bernhart in "Camille".
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 March 17; No. 868
    Will see you before you sail. Crocodile. To dine with Mrs. Gibbons.
  - Dallas Sanders to J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 March 20; No. 869
    Petitions for French Spoliation Claims (John Innes Clark against U.S. for ships Dolphin, Reemsdyke and Sukey.)
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 March 21; No. 870
    Keep Ava's picture till I get home. Will be home for week. When will you sail since you're not leaving now.
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 March 22; No. 871
    Mrs. Gibbons and Miss Whitney going to Europe for 2 years. Let's see Sarah Bernhart in "Cleopatra".
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 April 3; No. 872
    Arrived in snow storm.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 April 5; No. 873
    New Haven women presented Greek play - a great success.
  - ______ Pepper to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 April 9; No. 874
    Receipt for $6000. (to be invested in real estate in Chicago).
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 April 19; No. 875
    Thanks for figs and oranges. Send spring clothes. About Tom McKean and the horses in country. The grippe, dance and studies.
  - John L. Cadwalader to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 May 12; No. 876
    Sorry I missed you - if you are going abroad, come dine and I will start you off properly. About Emily at Biarritz.
  - Cass to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 June 1; No. 877
    Invitation to lunch in New York.
  - C. Willing Hare to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 June 2; No. 878
    In reference to us meeting Molly in New York.
  - N.P. to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 June 3; No. 879
    Advice on what to eat and drink.
  - Common Pleas Court No. 2 to Judge J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 June 13; No. 880
    Best wishes for safe and speedy voyage across Atlantic.
  - C.W. Hare to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 May 5; No. 880a
    Met Sally on train and went as far as New York with her. Columbia College theatrical group. Seniors Maypole dance.
  - Mary R. Coles to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 June 15; No. 881
    Not going to Class Day or boat race. Write to Aldersea.
  - Mary Robert Coles to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1891 June 17; No. 882
    Leaving for Aldersea tomorrow. Thanks for good times.
  - Mother to C. Willing Hare, 1891 June 18; No. 883
    Exams and tutor. Have given up going to boat race. Scolding for not paying bills.
  - Katharine W. Cheston to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 June 25; No. 884
    Sorry but can't visit Radnor now.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1891 July 1; No. 885
    Instructions on what to do at home and for the 4th.
  - Aunt Katie to Miss Esther Hare, 1891 July 5; No. 886
    Dreadful time with rooms. Took mud bath - frightening. About Grandmamma Beale. Food bad.
  - Grandpapa to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1891 July 10; No. 887
    Trouble finding rooms. Journey and cure have not improved health. A grave decision - if he remains cannot resume seat on bench and if he returns shall never again have opportunity of winter in Southern Europe. About Willing returning to Yale.
  - Katharine Livingston to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 July 11; No. 888
    Plan to meet you in Paris in autumn. Seeing other friends in Europe. Lovely trip in Italy - especially enjoyed Venice.
  - Emily Rawle to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 August 2; No. 889
    Expected to meet you in Paris - are you coming this autumn? General news of trip.
  - Mary R. Coles to Miss Esther Hare, 1891 August 3; No. 890
    Katharine Cheston with us. Having gay time - dances, tennis, riding, visits, dining, etc.
  - Mother to Miss E.B. Hare, 1891 August 11; No. 891
    Coming home.
  - D. Newton Fell to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 August 11; No. 892
    About court sessions and if it suits you, take November sessions.
  - Maimy to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 August 12; No. 893
    If you come abroad in fall, you must visit.
  - Katharine to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 August 15; No. 894
    Here to see plays.
  - E.B.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 August 24; No. 895
  - H.B.H. and Mother to Miss Hare, 1891 August 25; No. 896
    Activities and weather.
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 August 25; No. 897
    Paid bills, went to N.Y. with Sam Chew, saw "Beau Brummell", then went to New Haven about rooms. Cass's friend, Mr. Cameron, visiting. Letter from Aunt Connie saying she and Grandma will stay abroad, and probably Grandpa too.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 August 26; No. 898
    Redirested box from Howard and Co. Enclose bill from Geroud. Cass and Mr. Cameron (together so much in private). Home news.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 August 27; No. 899
    Ellen Harrison and Edith Wall visited and Ellen asked me to tea. Oliver and Aunt Katy arrived very late and I thought it was robbers. Cass and Mr. Cameron's flirtation very amusing.,
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1891 August 27; No. 900
    Instructions on keeping house at home. Katharine Cheston pretty and admired by all.
  - Cass to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1891 August 28; No. 901
    Misses you here terribly. About things at your home. Kate and Oliver, E. & W., and "Reverendy" Cameron's visit, (was so teased about him). Plans for trip to Geneva.
  - Mother to Miss E.B. Hare, 1891 August 28; No. 902
    (Private) Visitors, dinner at Dr. Chapman's and at the Rebo. Horace has been no where - flies kites all day. (Shocked to hear of Cass's proceedings.)
  - E. to Mrs. Beale, 1891 August 29; No. 903
    Mad rush - dinners, etc. Horace with me - independent in a boarding house across the way. Bay Hunt engaged to Mr. Slater. He has son and Enid engaged to him. Cass wants to join me abroad this winter, but I don't think it will work.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1891 September 2; No. 904
    Coming home, stopping at Portsmouth. Advising not to be extravagant keeping house and for Willing to study.
  - Nancy to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 September 2; No. 905
    Account of visit to Venice - (a glorious place) - palaces, terrible storm, etc. and plans of further travels.
  - Cass to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 September 4; No. 906
    Description of place and journey there. Evening in town with "Reverendy". Went to toy factory with Mrs. Cunningham and daughters Eleanor's music and Katherine's sketches.
  - Grandmama to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 September 5; No. 907
    Grandfather sick - confined to bed. In the "High Alps". Mr. and Mrs. Livingston and Kitty visited.
  - D. Newton Fell to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 September 8; No. 908
    Stay as long as you wish - Pennypacker and I will take care of the court sessions.
  - Samuel W. Pennypacker to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 September 10; No. 909
    Rely on Fell and myself to do court work. Remain where you are until entirely restored.
  - D. Newton Fell to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 September 10; No. 910
    Do not think of resigning. We can do the work and esteem it a privilege to relieve you while you take an indefinite furlough.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 September 14; No. 911
    Sorry, cannot be with your party this winter, but maybe could join "M.C." and Constance in St. Petersburgh. Ordered your Herbert's book. Willing's teasing - "never was so teased in my life before."
  - Joachim Beck Friis (?) to Mrs. Hare, 1891 September 23; No. 912
    Sincere thanks for pleasant visit in your home.
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 September 24; No. 913
    Passed exams and enter college "free from conditions". Coming home tomorrow. Box arrived and unpacked.
  - Thomas F. Davies to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1891 September 24; No. 914
    Thank you for your picture. Write from Europe. Pray you go and come in safety.
  - John L. Cadwalader to Mrs. Hare, 1891 October 6; No. 915
    Will stay in town late enough to see you before you leave.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 October; No. 916
    Sad at parting.
  - J.I. Clark Hare to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1891 October 4; No. 917
    Expect to see you in Italy and hope you will study and enjoy the wonders that lie open to you. And a letter from Constance to Emily telling of friends and where they are in Europe.
  - J.I. Clark Hare to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1891 October 7; No. 918
    Plans for your journey to Florence. Saw Queen of Romania several times (too weak to walk so brought down in chair), and also saw King of Italy who came to visit the Queen. Also a note from sister (C) explaining Mr. Hare's plans and to say Emily Welling will join you at Paris to come down.
  - Samuel Chew to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1891 October 7; No. 919
    Does not think he can come to New York to see you before you go abroad, but will if he can.
  - Maimy to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 October 8; No. 920
    About rooms there for you. Not much going on there this winter - in mourning for Grand Duchess. Wants Aunt Mary Anna and Connie to come too.
  - John T. Lewis & Brothers Co. to ________, 1891 October 5; No. 920a
    Account of monies due.
  - D. Newton Fell to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 October 20; No. 921
    Give up any thought of resigning, and stay abroad as long as it is of benefit to you. Court work being done.
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 October 22; No. 922
    Mr. Nichols not chosen for parish at St. Peter's in Philadelphia, rooms are comfortable, and about a fellow from New York (Harrison). Interested in taking singing lessons.
  - M. Mosby Williams to Hon. J.Innes Clark Hare, 1891 October 26; No. 923
    Request you fill out enclosed form. (Questionaire for "Genealogy of the Heirs of Harriet C. Hare")
  - D. Newton Fell to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 November 16; No. 924
    Court work being done, so stay abroad as long as you desire.
  - C.W.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 November 25; No. 925
    Tomorrow is Thanksgiving - going to Yale and Princeton football game in New York. Exercising and studying.
  - James T. Mitchell to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 December 8; No. 926
    Account of tribute to Judge Allison and hope you will not resign even though you are entitled to. Confidential talk with Governor on successor to Judge Clark (deceased) and conversation turned to rumor of your resignation. Court getting on easily, so don't come home until you're ready.
  - Samuel Chew to Miss Esther Hare, 1891 December 15; No. 927
    Sad that Yale beat us at football. Christmas wishes.
  - Maria to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 December 20; No. 928
    Enjoying Willing's company, but being in mourning cannot do anything pleasant for him. After Christmas going to devote myself to music.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 December 15; No. 929
    Among first 40 in class of 250. Going to Philadelphia tomorrow and will stay at Grandpapa's house.
  - Ethel Phelps to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1891 December 24; No. 930
    Piano and singing lessons, French, French history and riding. Plan to leave Paris in February, go up Nile and return by way of Italy and back to Paris the 1st of May.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1891 December 26; No. 931
    Accumulation of letters - Aug. 30 - to Mamma from Willing. Riding (sorry looking beast). Rode to Cabin Home and describes it. Shooting with Beau Westfeldt. Wants to see Vanderbilt's place. Request for clothes. (On a vacation, probably North Carolina. Sept. 30 - Mamma from Emily. Business to be attended to before starting abroad. Comments on Mr. Hare's health. Willing's rooms and exams. About Swedish diplomat met at Bar Harbor and invited to stay with us, and also a young Harvard fellow who came. Nov. 11 - To Mamma from C.W. Hare, New Haven. Asked Grandpapa to give you the house in town. General news of activities at college. Dec. 26 - Mamma from Willing, Philadelphia, Pa. Miss you so this Christmas. Comfortable at Grandpapa's. Social events and people attending. Aunt Katy and Uncle Oliver angry over something. Christmas gifts. Uncle Charley not well and going to California.
  - Wayne MacVeagh to J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 December 24; No. 932
    Will meet with friends on subject of your resignation, but foresee the result - ask you to retain your place until you are sure.
  - D. Newton Fell to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 December 29; No. 933
    Myself, Judge Pennypacker and Mr. MacVeagh agree that your resignation should not be sent to the Governor now.
  - Wayne MacVeagh to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 December 29; No. 934
    Dismiss the thought from your mind of resigning at present time.
  - Anna Tilghman to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 December 29; No. 935
    Maria, Betsy, William, myself and 2 servants have had influenza or grippe (an epidemic). All about family and friends. Ellen de Cuelebroeck.
  - Samuel W. Pennypacker to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1891 December 31; No. 936
    Mr. MacVeagh, Judge Fell and myself met and feel you should not resign now and continue your vacation until Fall if you wish. Work being done satisfactorily.
  - Cass to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1892 January 5; No. 937
    On loneliness (much about Faith in God and you'll never be alone). Her feeling's about "Reverendy's" engagement. An accident (fall) made everyone so attentive to me.
  - Katherine W. Cheston to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1892 January 6; No. 938
    Uncle and Grandmother Cheston died, so will not "come out" until next winter (we will be debutantes together). About friends.
  - _______ ? to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1892 January 13; No. 939
    Activities since you left.
  - W.W. Montgomery (nephew) to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, 1892 January 15; No. 940
    On business. Enclosed blank power of attorney and blank check. Also account. Rev. Hunt resigned rectorship of St. Martins due to ill health and succeeded by Rev. W.S. Baer.
  - George Hall, Jr. to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1892 January 28; No. 940a
  - Sarah to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1892 January 17; No. 941
    About Willing at home for holidays.
  - Sarah and Bridget to Mrs. J.I.C. Hare, 1892 January 17; No. 942
    On Willing at home for holidays. About house and things at home.
  - Katharine W. Cheston to Miss Esther Hare, 1892 January 19; No. 943
    About Molly's looks on the night of the 1st Assembly. Also a description of Virginia and Mary Thorndike and the dinner and flowers.
  - Mary Robert Coles to Miss E.B. Hare, 1892 January 20; No. 944
    Willing and social events (1st Assembly and Ellen Harrison's dance and other events.) Fire at Williams on 15th St.
  - Willing Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 January 27; No. 945
    Very gay during holidays. Harrison's Ball - description of decorations, girls and their clothes, etc.
  - Willing Hare to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1892 February 16; No. 946
    Met Miss Cheston at Molly's tea. Ellen Harrison and Edyth Wain getting attention because Mother's entertain so much. Poor Molly Coles and Virginia have "ratty looking men attentive to them". Miss Fischer and Miss Tyson "the belles". Sam sick during holidays. William's dance very stupid. William's fire. Mr. Welling, Cass's father, died. Uncle Charlie dissatisfied with America set sail for the "old world". Mr. Nichols "called" to a church in St. Louis.
  - George Hall, Jr. to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1892 February 29; No. 947
    Statement of account. Have not been able to rent either house, 120 S. 22nd St. or 254 S. 21st.
  - Horace to Mrs. Hare, 1892 March 9; No. 948
    When will Trux be able to go out. Impossible to see Pope.
  - W.W. Montgomery (nephew) to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, 1892 March 18; No. 949
    Acct. of Drexel & Co., and explanation of his account with you.
  - Mildred to Esther Hare, 1892 March 20; No. 950
    About being in Venice and now in Paris, riding and driving.
  - Horace to Mrs. Hare, 1892 March 21; No. 951
    Visit to a volcano.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1892 March 23; No. 952
    Doctor took Truxtun's nurse, but she returned in a few hours. Queen passed by. Sightseeing and shopping. Got flowers from Shelly and Keat's graves.
  - C.W. Hare to Hon. J.I.C. Hare, 1892 March 24; No. 953
    Has been "suspended", but thinks with tutors can pass exams in June. Awaiting your decision.
  - E.B.M. to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, 1892 March 24; No. 954
    Alice, Bertha and I have been bedfast. Miserable weather. Family and friends.
  - Nannie Gilpin to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1892 March 26; No. 955
    Rush to get there and what they are doing.
  - Horace B. Hare to Master T. Truxtun Hare, 1892 March 27; No. 956
    What he's doing - volcano, Pompeii, Vesuvius and Sorrento.
  - Horace Binney Hare to Mrs. Hare, 1892 March 27; No. 957
    Glad to hear of Truxton's first walk. Bay of Naples, Pompeii, and Grandpapa found rooms at Sorrento. Aunt C. is much better.
  - Charlotte Coxe to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1892 March 28; No. 958
    Papa bought house on Spruce St. Grandmama's house being torn down. All about friends and activities.
  - Zempt Freres to Mrs. Hare, 1892 March; No. 959
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1892 March 28; No. 960
    Sent photo to Willing. Gave up salon and bedroom and moving into nurse's room to cut expenses. Gave Mazzieri "a piece of my mind".
  - Mary Harrison to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1892 April 4; No. 961
    Father returned to Americabut will join us for summer. Met Daisy and Mr. Whitewash in Venice and Paris several times. Sorry to hear of Truxton's scarlet fever. Trip north to Holland.
  - Emily Rawle to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 April 7; No. 962
    Might possibly meet you in Paris in autumn. Public fighting Traction Co. who want to run street cars with overhead electric wires in Phila. Inquiries of Ducky's illness.
  - Esther to Mrs. Hare, 1892 April 10; No. 963
    See if you can get me a straw sailor hat. My shirt is lost.
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1892 April 15; No. 964
    Just got word you have consented to my studying at Milford under tutor. Sorry for "suspension". Will study hard.
  - Lily to Mrs. Hare, 1892 April 17; No. 965
    Easter card.
  - E.B.M. (sister) to Mrs. Hare, 1892 April 18; No. 966
    Sorry for you and Truxtun confined with scarlet fever, and concern over Constance's bronchitia. News of family and friends.
  - Willing Hare to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1892 April 19; No. 967
    Uncle Ned coming up, and I go Thursday to Milford to live with clergyman. Hope to "pull" through and get back with class.
  - Andrew to Hon. J.I.C. Hare, 1892 April 22; No. 968
    Care of the place at home - cows, horses, dogs and planting.
  - Katharine W. Cheston to Miss Esther Binney Hare, 1892 April 30; No. 969
    Thank you for photo. Going abroad with Bessy Farnum and then going to join Aunt and Uncle. Went to New Orleans to Mardi Gras and Florida. Concerts and theatre. To Boston for a wedding. About Molly.
  - W.W. Montgomery (nephew) to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, 1892 May 6; No. 970
    Paying taxes and about bond. Man helping Andrew, and new preacher at St. Martins.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1892 May 8; No. 971
    Arrived Palermo. Exposition poor and stupid.
  - C.H. to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, 1892 May 8; No. 972
    On journey with Constance, Mrs. Beale and Emily. Emily unhappy. Will meet you in Sorrento. Keep boys studying. Going to Taormina.
  - C.H. to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, 1892 May 11; No. 973
    Pleasant trip - taking it easy for health.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1892 May 13; No. 974
    Nice journey here but want to be with you. Grandpapa enjoying everything.
  - Aunt Constance to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1892 May 13; No. 975
    Stockings. Grandpapa enjoying himself so much, but your Mother and I impatient to get north.
  - Mother to Miss Hare, 1892 May 16; No. 976
    Wanted to come to you sooner, but have to wait till all come. Aunt Katy has a little boy.
  - C.W. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 May 22; No. 977
    Request to stay at "Harford", Radnor, Pennsylvania this summer. Doing best at lessons, but as Grandpapa says "deeds not words must show in the future". Clipping enclosed on death of classmate.
  - Albert Stopford to Mrs. Hare, 1892 May 27; No. 978
    Been busy moving into house.
  - Horace B. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 June 4; No. 979
    Met Miss Brown and two Chew girls. Leave tomorrow for Bolognia and then to Venice. Saw national ball game of Italy.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 June 6; No. 980
    Saw all old friends at Rome. Journey from Rome to Florence. "Doings" and friends. Sam Chew inherited old homestead "Cliveden" and Ben Chew speaks of Sam as "Esther's devoted".
  - Axel Muntry ? to Mrs. Hare, 1892 June 26; No. 981
    Advising you to take your boys out of Italy and go to Switzerland. If necessary get Miss Yanes ? to take care of him.
  - Violet M. Hope to Miss Hare, 1892 July 3; No. 982
    Sights they are seeing.
  - Supplement de La Revue, 1892 July 9; No. 983
  - 2nd Supplement - Journal de Vevey., 1892 July 9; No. 984
  - Horace B. Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 July 13; No. 985
    The place and people there. Truxton delighted with suit.
  - George Hall, Jr. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 July 14; No. 986
    Statement of your account.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 July 16; No. 987
    Miss you. Accounts of people seen. Had woman about hats (she put mine on and I can "never take it off") She was very entertaining. Silk arrived - what shall I do with it? New maid. Tracy's visited me.
  - E.C.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1892 July 18; No. 988
    Request you find Rudolph Meyer at Carlsbad and inquire about box that was to be sent. Your Mother arrived safely. Hope you will be better "for the cure."